divatress.com 2012-01-07

# Privacy Policy

#### You're currently on:

### Privacy Policy

Thank you for visiting our web site. Divatress.com respects your privacy. This privacy policy tells you how we use personal information collected at this site. Please read this privacy policy before using the site or submitting any personal information. By using the site, you are accepting the practices described in this privacy policy. These practices may be changed, but any changes will be posted and changes will only apply to activities and information on a going forward, not retroactive basis. You are encouraged to review the privacy policy whenever you visit the site to make sure that you understand how any personal information you provide will be used.

Note: the privacy practices set forth in this privacy policy are for this web site only. If you link to other web sites, please review the privacy policies posted at those sites.

##### Collection of Information

Divatress.com collects information about website visitors to provide and improve our services, communicate offers which we believe will interest site visitors, and to administer our business.

The information we collect on Divatress.com may be used to fulfill your requests (such as product orders and responses to email questions) and to communicate with you about our product offers and promotions.

If you create or modify a Divatress.com account you may save personal information in that account, such as name, shipping and billing addresses, and credit card information, and we will access this saved information to make your shopping quicker and easier. We also require you to create and/or access your account to use various services on the website, including creating a product review. Because you must create or access your Divatress.com account prior to creating a review, it is possible that we could associate you with the review you provide. Information you include in a product review may be used by us to enhance and personalize our product offerings to you.

##### Cookie/Tracking Technology

Divatress.com may use cookie and tracking technology depending on the features offered. Cookie and tracking technology are useful for gathering information such as browser type and operating system, tracking the number of visitors to the Site, and understanding how visitors use the Site. Cookies can also help customize the Site for visitors. Personal information cannot be collected via cookies and other tracking technology, however, if you previously provided personally identifiable information, cookies may be tied to such information. Aggregate cookie and tracking information may be shared with third parties.

##### Third Parties

Authorized third parties may need access to some of your personal information. For example, if Divatress.com needs to ship a product to you, we must share your name and address with a shipping company. Divatress.com needs limit such third parties in their access and use of your personal information. Divatress.com does not otherwise share your personal information with third parties, unless you grant us permission to do so.

##### Public Forums

Please remember that any information you may disclose in public areas of our website or the Internet becomes public information. You should exercise caution when deciding to disclose personal information in these public areas.

##### Commitment to Data Security

Your personally identifiable information is kept secure. Only authorized employees, agents and contractors (who have agreed to keep information secure and confidential) have access to this information. All emails and newsletters from this site allow you to opt out of further mailings.

##### Privacy Contact Information

If you have any questions, concerns, or comments about our privacy policy you may contact us using the information below:

  * By email to: customercare@divatress.com
  * By phone to: 1-877-DIVATRESS

We reserve the right to make changes to this policy. Any changes to this policy will be posted.
